[{"answer": "Hello, Piers.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "Donald, how are you?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "Well, it wasn't a good one.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "What do you make of the basic substance of this debate, which is whether Mitt Romney's record at Bain Capital was predominantly a good one or a bad one?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "Well, I've been supporting him for a long time.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "But isn't one of the problems here, Donald, that people like you and Newt Gingrich who are now racing to support Mitt Romney over this battle have in the past attacked him for his record at Bain?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, we're not $13 or $14 trillion in debt, we're $16 trillion in debt and going up rapidly.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "But is it the right battle ground for Mitt Romney, do you think?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I know Cory Booker.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "Do you think it's too vicious or do you think this is part and parcel of American political life?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "Well, a book was just written by a great writer named Ed Kline.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "Now, are you saying that it would be fair game to go after President Obama based on his association with that man?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "I think the Democrats will use whatever they can use regardless of whether or not Reverend Wright is brought up.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "But clearly if Reverend Wright comes into play and is deemed to be fair game, then wouldn't it be also fair game to go after Mitt Romney for his religion?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "No, I think it's very cute, it's fun.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "Do you think it's a fairly silly way of attacking him?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "Well, look.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "What do you think of that argument?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "So many people have asked me that question lately.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "If Mitt Romney asked you what would you say?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think he's going to ask me, but certainly I have a very strong base of people that do like what I say.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "Including saying yes to VP if he asked you?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "Well, a lot of people have been asking me whether or not I'd be interested in doing it.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "Have you been asked to speak at the Republican convention this summer and if so will you say yes if you are?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "Well, I don't like, frankly, what he did to Ryan Seacrest.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "What have you got against Sacha Baron Cohen?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "I'm doing just fine.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "Gregg, how are you?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "Just great.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "Does it feel good to be alive?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "That's the way I feel.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "Is that how you feel?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "Just to have fun making music.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 410, "question": "Or was it just to have fun making music?", "qSentId": 409}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "Everything just came as a kind of accidental side effect of that love for music?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "Drugs.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "When you finished the book did you sit back and go, I wish I hadn't done that?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "Drugs and alcohol.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "You wish you never got involved with drugs?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "They make you crazy.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "What did they do to you, do you think?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "Do you still get as much fun from playing music as you always did?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "Yes, sir.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "Is it the one constant in your life?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "Well, I've gone on stage before three times with an abscessed tooth, and I got there and set down behind my ax and started playing.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "What does it do for you when it's just you and the music?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "Don't even feel the pain of an abscessed tooth?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "In your book.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "Where does it say that?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "Does it?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 455, "question": "A scoop on your hands?", "qSentId": 454}, {"answer": "Two, three people.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "Does anybody else know this?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "She is 24.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "How old is your fiance?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "That's not what she's becoming.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "And how does she feel about becoming wife number seven?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "Well, because this time I am really in love.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "What made you take the plunge again?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "Like you've never been before?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "Those one sided, I think twice.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "How many times do you think you've been properly in love?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 488, "question": "You were only in love with two of your six wives?", "qSentId": 487}, {"answer": "That would be a scoop.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "I'm assuming that was a compliment, right?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "You were in love with Cher, weren't you?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "From time to time, yes.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "Have you said in touch with her?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "Are you a good friend?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "It was a hideous experience.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "Was that a hideous experience?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "Oh, man.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "Because the whole world wants a piece of you, right?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "And how much of it was your fault that you kept having broken marriages, do you think?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "You got down on bended knee?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "Do you remember your exact words?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "Shannon.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "What is her name?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "When are you getting married?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 562, "question": "Do you think Shannon knows the real dude?", "qSentId": 561}, {"answer": "I think it's totally irrelevant.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 566, "question": "Is that -- do you think that is a good thing?", "qSentId": 565}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "You sing to her?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "I would like to be remembered as a -- somebody who could rock your soul or make your cry with a song.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "How would you like to be remembered?", "qSentId": 579}, {"answer": "Yes, including on this side of the Atlantic impeaching a president.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "It just kept coming, didn't it?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think it inevitably has to go into more partisanship.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "Or do you think the networks can still stay strong down the middle?", "qSentId": 610}, {"answer": "ESTIN: I think there's nothing wrong with opinion journalism.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 621, "question": "Is it -- is it extensively unhealthy to have partisan cable networks?", "qSentId": 620}, {"answer": "Exactly right.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 630, "question": "You mean where news is presented in the opinionated manner?", "qSentId": 629}, {"answer": "Well, it changed fundamentally.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "Did it become more fractious?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "Yes, although my -- this is my personal opinion now, and I'm not responsible for covering these things, my reaction to the Cory Booker issue was he can support President Obama and not agree with him on every single thing.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 673, "question": "you basically had it for the short term, doesn't he?", "qSentId": 672}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, on a personal note, I mean, the death of Peter Jennings was a terrible moment and then the wounding of Bob Woodruff and his cameramen, Dough Vogt, in Iraq were awful.", "docId": "120522pmt", "aSentId": 707, "question": "And what was the lowest moment?", "qSentId": 706}]